Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer And Deliverance In Jesus' Name
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
I won't talk.
She's my wife.
What have you done to her?
She will never marry because she is mine.
What have you done to her family?
Stagnation, limitation - she will never use her certificate.
What have you done to her career?
She will be working and resigning.
She just resigned from Samsung.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY TIME
Children of God, shout Emmanuel for me!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
I'm here to thank God for my deliverance
by the touch of the man of God because it was a Heavenly touch.
My name is Iwuchukwu Vivian.
It all started when my father died.
Everything went wrong
because my father was the breadwinner then.
He helped his brothers. When he died, all of them refused to help us.
One of them told us - the one in Germany, a medical doctor -
that we should leave where we were staying and go to the village.
I was kind of stubborn because of that spiritual husband.
So I refused.
I said, "I'm in school already and my younger ones are not going to stop schooling.
I will find the means for us to continue our studies".
One of my friends told me that there was a party at the government house at Owerri.
I studied logistics management technology at the University of Technology in Owerri.
So we went to the party - it was a gala night.
He told me that at that party, they would give 'thanks for coming'.
What I mean by 'thanks for coming' is: if you meet a man or not, they would give you money.
It was a caucus of senators and commissioners.
At that party I met a commissioner.
He became my friend.
That's how staying with married men started.
The man was kind of assisting me, helping me.
That's how I was able to assist my younger ones.
It continued. There was this thing I noticed about myself:
Anywhere I went to - before I was delivered -
there was this spirit that got men to be attracted to me.
When they came and we exchanged contacts,
I would be in the house and they would call me. I would go and meet them.
After sleeping with them, they would give me money.
So I would go home with it and continue my life.
The money I gathered, I used It to start little business whilst being in school like selling clothes.
I kept doing that until I finished university.
When I moved to Port Harcourt, I met new friends.
After my studies, I started work.
Like the stupid spiritual husband said:
I never used my certificate. As I worked, I resigned.
It's true because I worked for four good companies with a good job
but I ended up resigning for no reason.
I resigned on my own. Even the last one, I resigned from the company I was working for.
I left my work. I don't know about other companies but in this company,
you have to give one month notice before you can leave the company.
But I couldn't do that. I had to just forfeit my salary and resigned.
I resigned; nobody sacked me.
I know that some from my office are watching me and they know what I'm saying.
So after resigning, did you actually come back to your senses
or what normally happened after you voluntarily resigned from your job?
Still the 'men business'.
Whenever I went to the market, it was like that time it became more serious than before.
Whenever I wanted to go to the market or church,
or maybe board a cab to where I was going to,
I would just see a car by my side.
It would be a very expensive car - a machine, not just a car.
So when they stopped, I would exchange contacts.
Maybe they were not going in the direction I was going to or I was not in the mood at that moment.
I would take a complimentary card or contacts.
They would give me a call. They would be the ones to call.
They would keep disturbing me because of that spiritual husband.
It's not like I knew what I was doing.
I knew myself but what was wrong, what attracted all those things is what I didn't know.
If they were shopping for me, I would tell them, "Let me see the picture of your wife.
Why don't you shop for your wife too".
So they would say, "Ok, this is the picture".
I would pick clothes - good clothes - or shoes.
Then the man would go home with it and give it to his wife.
The wife would think it was the husband that bought it.
No, it was the girlfriend outside who initiated that.
So that would make them to be more interested and come even closer to me.
So at that point when I got money, I didn't know what I used it for.
It was just for shopping.
Whenever I payed my bills or spent it on family issues, I was left with nothing.
So I decided, "Ok, let me just save up money and start a business.
At least I know how to style hair".
A particular man - he had spoken twice to me before -
the day that I called him that I needed money for something,
he told me that it was like I had a spiritual husband.
I said, "I have been hearing about this kind of thing".
I knew something was wrong with me but I didn't know what it was.
I agreed to go.
He set a date and we went to a place - somewhere in Enugu State.
When we entered, we reached a point where nothing like a motorcycle or car was passing.
It was a bush.
We started entering, and I asked, "What is this? Exactly where are we going to?"
At the top of this hill was an ocean or river.
People were there - plenty of people.
When you got there, they would call your name and start telling you why you came and all that.
So I was there.
They told me what I was going to pay so that they would remove the spiritual husband,
and also open my way so that things would not be difficult for me anymore.
They said I should pay N320,000.
I ended up spending that money there.
And that money - it was not that I spent it or they were using it -
they would tear the money into four pieces, throw it into the ocean and say some things.
Before then, they said that there were some things they needed to get
for me to bath in that ocean on top of that hill.
During the bath, I would do some sacrifice.
They mentioned chicken and all that. Fanta, precisely.
So when they mentioned all those things,
I said, "I can't bring all those things, I don't know where to bring it from".
They said, "Okay, pay the money. We will bring it for you".
I paid.
The money I was saving up - I ended up spending all.
So they bathed me and in the process of bathing me, they cut my hair.
They cut my nails - my toenails and my fingernails.
After performing all these sacrifices, what happened?
Were you able to make any headway towards all the problems you were encountering in your life?
My sister, nothing.
So how did you end up knowing about The SCOAN?
That you now came here and you received your deliverance?
When I was at home and I woke up from sleep -
I am the type that likes watching movies.
So I started watching a movie.
After the movie finished, there was nothing else to watch.
I was flipping through TV channels.
Prophet T.B. Joshua's channel came up.
He was saying, "Viewers all over the world" - he was praying on TV.
You mean Emmanuel TV?
Yes, Emmanuel TV.
So I prayed along with him. After praying along with him, I slept.
Something like a light came, flashed on my eyes and slapped me.
When the thing slapped me, it was like something came out of my eyes.
So I jumped up.
It was around 4 am. It was already getting to daybreak.
So as I woke up, I said, "What is this? What kind of dream is this?"
I just said a short prayer and lay down again.
In the morning, I started getting my brain back.
I started realising that it was true. That I had spent all my money on nonsense.
That what was I going to do now?
What was going on? Where was I going to start from now?
Was I to start with men again and all that?
Because that was the only point, that was what I could fall back on again.
I said to myself that I still had little money in my account.
That this was maybe because I had prayed with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua on Emmanuel TV.
Let me just go there.
I went to a hotel and booked my ticket to Lagos last week.
So when I came, that's when the man of God touched me.
At that point I didn't even know where I was, I didn't know what happened next.
I just saw someone coming.
But before then, when he was coming, I was shivering. I noticed that I wasn't myself anymore.
As I was standing, the next thing I saw was a hammer on my head.
I looked. I had a complete blackout. I didn't know what happened till now.
I thank God so much.
So what are the changes that you have seen since your deliverance?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
You know this deliverance is of a thing... People are used to hear of deliverance.
When you are delivered, you yourself will know that you are delivered.
You feel this joy.
On that day when I was delivered, some people - I don't know whether they are here,
they may be watching me, the people that were in the church last week.
I was so excited.
My body was sweating as if I had won something somewhere.
I'm now okay. I'm free. I sleep well. I wake up well. I don't have those thoughts anymore.
They don't even call. I've deleted all their numbers.
I'm intending to change my telephone number.
And what about the spiritual husband that used to torment you in your dreams?
That one - he has gone back to where he came from.
To the pit of hell!
Shall we put our hands together for Jesus!
We give glory to God Almighty for this wonderful deliverance that you have received.
What do you want to advise people that are listening to your wonderful testimony?
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My advice goes to young men and young ladies:
To be frank, all these we are seeing while being on campus...
First of all, choose your friends. Don't let your friends choose you.
Secondly, if you're a young girl, and you noticed...
I'm not giving this testimony to entice you.
I'm giving it and praying to God that this testimony will change a soul
because then I was in the world; now I'm a new creation.
I'm not ashamed of my testimony.
I'm so proud of myself because I have finally made it.
And I know that I am okay. I also pray that any young lady that is listening to me here,
please go to a living church.
If you are not sure of any, run to The SCOAN -
just the same way I used my last money and paid for my flight ticket to this place.
Come here and you will get your deliverance.
And also your salvation will increase.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
My name is Vivian Iwuchukwu. I am from Port Harcourt.
What brought me to the church was my deliverance, which I have gotten.
I thank God. I'm delivered now, and I'm okay.
I was in the congregation when the man of God was touching people at the side where I was.
He touched me, and the spiritual husband inside of me manifested.
He was saying that I will not use my certificate,
I will not get married and that I will be working and resigning,
which I confirmed to be true.
I also thank God that after the deliverance, I'm now okay,
my dreams are fine, everything is okay.
The evil spirit pushed me to be with married men.
I stayed with them, they gave me money.
At the end of the day, I couldn't give account of the money.
When I was working, I resigned from four companies.
When I resigned from the last company, I had to run to God for help
because I didn't know what was happening to me anymore.
I was eating in my dreams. At times, I would be at a riverside or ocean.
At times, I would have an affair in my dreams.
Since your deliverance at The SCOAN, after Prophet T.B. Joshua had prayed for you,
tell us how your life has changed.
Now I am a new person. I feel so happy inside my heart, inside of me.
I sleep very well. My dreams are fine.
I sleep singing in my dreams, and I wake up singing.
Reading the Bible is now part of me.
I always meditate with my faith bracelet.
It is always with me which is helping me to build my faith more,
to maintain my deliverance and my salvation.
By the grace of God, I want to be self-employed and independent,
make money myself and help my family instead of going the other way round.
To God be the glory. We thank God Almighty for what He has done in your life.
Prophet T.B. Joshua and the Emmanuel TV partners are very much concerned about you
and the next step that you want to take in Christ Jesus,
to make sure that you continue to make the Word of God the standard for your life.
They are supporting you with this sum of 200,000 naira.
Vivian Receives N200,000 From T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Partners To Start A New Life In Christ
I want to thank God for this and also thank the man of God so much
because this is a new beginning and I know this money is coming from the altar
and it will go a long way. It will bear fruits - more than the money out there.
I'm so happy to start my life with this.
I want to tell the man of God: May the Almighty God keep him for us
because he is the prophet of our generation.
His family - favour befall them. He will grow from strength to strength,
anointing to anointing, grace to grace.
Heaven will always be with him.
I thank God for his life, and I promise him I'll make it up to him.
I'll make him proud with this, in Jesus' name.
Amen. To God be the glory.
We pray that God Almighty gives you that grace to stay far from sin
and close to Him as you continue to make God's Word the standard for your life.
So lastly, give a word of advice to people watching you all over the world.
My advice to people like I said on Sunday:
To ladies - if you notice that something is wrong with you
and maybe you are going off track, please run to God.
He is the only solution. He is the only way for you to have peace of mind.
Please emulate the Word of God. That's the only way out.
With your Bible, call on the Holy Spirit. He will see you through.
Amen. We want to encourage you too that it is not all about the situation you are facing,
nor where you are but who you are in Christ Jesus that really matters.
Everyone faces common challenges and calamities of life
but what makes you a Christian, what makes you a child of God
is not what you go through, but how you go through them.
So continue to choose God's way and not the way of the world
and the best is yet to come for you and your family, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Thank you.
Thank You, Jesus, I am free. Thank You, Holy Spirit, for this opportunity.
Thank you because I'll make good use of it, in Jesus' name. Amen
Vivian Receives N200,000 From T.B. Joshua And Emmanuel TV Partners To Start A New Life In Christ